9to5: Days in Porn is a documentary film directed by Jens Hoffmann.
9to5 - Days in Porn focuses on the people behind a controversial and
multi-billion dollar industry "The Adult Entertainment industry".
It depicts their stories, each one different, unadorned and
authentic, without glorification or prejudice.
It delivers deep insight into their personal lives - from glamorous to grotesque -
strange, fascinating, offensive, absurd and sometimes funny moments all at once.
Self, played by Monique Alexander.
Self, played by Joanna Angel.
Self, played by Jesse Jane.
Self, played by Sandee Westgate.
Self, played by Belladonna.
Self, played by Sasha Grey.
9 to 5: Days in Porn, also known as The Porn Diaries (UK), is a 2008 English-language German
documentary film about the United States porn industry, written and directed by Jens Hoffmann.
The film explores themes of pornography, eroticism, porn industry.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.